Guide to the William F. Wu Comics Collection MSS.244
Fales Library and Special Collections
William F. Wu Comics Collection
1920-2001
Fales Library and Special Collections
Wu, William F., 1951-
MSS.244
11 Linear Feet in 10 record cartons and 2 flat boxes.
William F. Wu is an Asian American scholar and science fiction writer whose doctoral dissertation titled The Yellow Peril (1981) documents evolving depictions of Chinese and Chinese-Americans in American fiction. This archive represents his collection of nearly 600 comics featuring Asian characters.
Arrangement
The William F. Wu Comics Collection is organized into eight series, arranged primarily by publishing company. Subseries are arranged by character or comic. Many of the character subseries are pulled from titles written on cardboard dividers that Wu used in his own organization of the comics. Subseries based on comics contain multiple issues of the same title, and feature different characters.
The collection is arranged into eight series:
Series I: Marvel Asian (By Character)
Series II: Marvel Asian (By Comic)
Series III: DC Asian (By Character)
Series IV: DC Asian (By Comic)
Series V: Deadly Hands of Kung Fu
Series VI: Charlton Comics
Series VII: Various Comics
Series VIII: 2018 Accretion
Biographical Note
William F. Wu is a Chinese-American science-fiction writer who has published thirteen novels and more than fifty short stories. Born in Kansas City, Missouri, Wu attended the University of Michigan as an undergraduate, and later returned to earn his Ph.D in American Culture. During this time he became active in East Wind, an Asian American student group. His doctoral dissertation titled The Yellow Peril (1981) documents evolving depictions of Chinese and Chinese-Americans in American fiction.
Wu has been nominated for the Nebula Award, World Fantasy Award and the Hugo Award, twice individually and once as a member of the Wild Cards. Hong on the Range, set in a futuristic version of the wild west, was chosen for the Wilson Library Bulletin's list of science fiction "Books Too Good To Miss" and was a selection for the American Library Association list of Best Books for Young People, the New York Public Library's Recommended Books for the Teen Age, and was also a Young Adult Editor's Choice by Booklist Magazine.
(Source: http://dlibdev.nyu.edu/tamimentapa/?q=node/106)
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of comic books with Asian characters, collected by William F. Wu over the course of several years. Spanning the years 1920 to 2001, the books contain an abundance of representations of Asians in popular American culture. Many stereotypical depictions of Asians and Asian Americans - such as "Chinamen" and martial arts experts - are present, as are characters with exaggeratedly "Asian" features. Many of the comics also contain advertisements for martial arts books and courses. Although most of the comics were published by well-known comic book companies such as DC Comics, Marvel, Atlas and Charlton, comics from smaller companies such as Wings Publishing Company, Real Adventures Publishing Company and Rotten Comics are also included. Titles include Superman, Iron Man, Spiderman, Batman, Jonah Hex, The Justice League of America, Yang, Deadly Hands of Kung Fu, Weird War Tales, Godzilla, Doctor Strange, and Starfire. The earliest comics in the collection are Pulp magazines, Captain Marvel, and Green Hornet. There are printed compilations of both Will Gould's Red Barry and Doctor Strange comics, as well as a number of original splash pages of the Master of Kung Fu and What If? comics.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by William F. Wu in 2009 and 2018. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 2009.244 and 2018.062.
Asian Americans -- Ethnic identity.; Comic books.; Racism.; Wu, William F., 1951-
- Series I: Marvel Asian (By Character), 166112
  - Subseries A: Ancient One/ Wong, 166272
    - Dr. Strange Master of the Mystic Arts (1), June 1974; 212203 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Dr. Strange Master of the Mystic Arts (2-7), August 1974- April 1975; 212204 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dr. Strange Master of the Mystic Arts (8-13), June 1975- April 1976; 212205 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dr. Strange Master of the Mystic Arts (14-17), May- August 1976; 212206 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dr. Strange Master of the Mystic Arts (18-21), September 1976- February 1977; 212207 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dr. Strange Master of the Mystic Arts (25-26), October - December 1977; 212208 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Dr. Strange Master of the Mystic Arts (38,39,42), December 1979- August 1980; 212209 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Marvel Premiere feat. Dr. Strange (3-7), July 1972- March 1975; 212210 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Marvel Premiere feat. Dr. Strange (8,10,11,13,14), May 1993- March 1974; 212211 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Strange Tales feat. Doctor Strange (182,184,185), November 1975- May 1976; 212212 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Strange Tales feat. Dr. Strange (186-188), July- November 1976; 212213 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Dr. Strange (King- Size Annual) (1), 1976; 212214 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Doctor Strange (22,23), April- June 1977; 212215 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Doctor Strange (43,44), October- December 1980; 212216 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Doctor Strange (1), March 1982; 212217 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - The Essential Doctor Strange (1), 2001; 212218 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - The Defenders (1-2, 4-6), August 1972- June 1973; 212219 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - The Defenders (8, 10-13), September 1973- May 1974; 212220 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Marvel Feature Presents the Defenders (1-3), December 1971- June 1972; 212221 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Giant-Size Defenders (1), July 1974; 212222 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - The Tomb of Dracula Lord of Vampires (44), May 1976; 212223 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - What if Dr. Strange Were A Disciple of Dormammu? (18), December 1979; 212224 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Subseries B: Fin Fang Foom, 212164
    - Where Monsters Dwell (21), May 1973; 212226 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Fantasy Masterpieces (2,5,6), April- December 1966; 212227 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C: Philip Chang, 212165
    - The Amazing Spider-Man (184,185), September- October 1978; 212228 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Peter Parker The Spectacular Spider-Man (19), June 1978; 212229 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Peter Parker the Spectacular Spider-Man (36,38), November 1979- Jan 1980; 212230 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Peter Parker the Spectacular Spiderman (49), December 1980; 212231 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Subseries D: The Mandarin, 212166
    - Iron Man (9-11, 57-58), January 1969- April 1973; 212232 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Iron Man (99-101), June- August 1977; 212233 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Tales of Suspense feat. The Power of Iron Man (55), July 1964; 212234 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Tales of Suspense: Iron Man and Captain America (76,77,85,86), April 1966- February 1967; 212235 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Marvel Double Feature: Captain America and Iron Man (2-3), February- April 1974; 212236 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Captain America (125), May 1970; 212237 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - The Inhumans and the Black Widow (3-4), November 1970- January 1971; 212238 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Giant Size Avengers (5), 1975; 212239 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - The Incredible Hulk (62), January 1977; 212240 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Subseries E: Sha- Shan, 212167
    - Peter Parker the Spectacular Spider-Man (3), February 1977; 212243 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Peter Parker The Spectacular Spider Man (4,5,7,8), March- July 1977; 212244 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Peter Parker the Spectacular Spider-Man (10,12-14), September 1977- January 1978; 212245 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Marvel Tales Starring Spiderman (87-88), January- February 1978; 212246 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - The Amazing Spider-Man (109), June 1972; 212247 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Subseries F: Silver Samurai, 212168
    - Spiderman and the Not-Ready-for-Prime-Time Players (74), October 1978; 212248 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Spiderman and Nick Fury (83), July 1979; 212249 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Daredevil (111), July 1974; 212264 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Subseries G: Sunfire, 212169
    - Iron Man (68-71), June- November 1974; 212250 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Iron Man (98), May 1977; 212251 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - X-Men (94), August 1975; 212252 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - X-Men (118-119), February- March 1979; 212253 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Giant Size X-Men (1), 1975; 212254 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Sub-Mariner (52-54), August- October 1972; 212255 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - The Avengers (117), November 1973; 212256 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Subseries H: Yellow Claw, 212170
    - Yellow Claw (1), October 1956; 212263 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Avengers (204-205), February 1981- March 1981); 212257 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - The Man Called Nova (16-18), December 1977- March 1978; 212260 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - What if the Avengers Had Fought Evil During the 1950's? (9), June 1978; 212261 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Captain America And the Fallon (165- 167), November 1973; 212262 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Series II: Marvel Asian (By Comic), 212171
  - Subseries A: Daredevil, 212266
    - Daredevil (175-176), October- November 1981; 212267 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Daredevil and the Black Widow (92), October 1972; 212268 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Godzilla, 212172
    - Godzilla King of the Monsters (1-3, 5), August- December 1977; 212281 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Godzilla King of the Monsters (6-10), January- May 1978; 212282 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Godzilla King of the Monsters (11-15), June- October 1978; 212283 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Godzilla King of the Monsters (16-20), November- March 1979; 212284 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Godzilla King of the Monsters (22-24), May- July 1979; 212285 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Subseries C: Iron Fist, 212173
    - Iron Fist (1-6), November 1975- August 1976; 212286 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Iron Fist (7-11), September 1976- February 1977; 212293 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Iron Fist (12-15), April- September 1977; 212294 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Power Man and Iron Fist (50-55), April 1978- February 1979; 212295 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Power Man and Iron Fist (59-63), October 1979- June 1980; 212296 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Power Man and Iron Fist (66,67,75,83), December 1980- July 1982; 212297 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Power Man and Iron Fist (119), September 1985; 212298 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Mavel Premiere feat. Iron Fist (15-21), May 1974- March 1975; 212322 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Marvel Premiere feat. Iron Fist (22-25), June- October 1975; 212288 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Hulk and Power Man and Iron Fist (3), 1980; 212289 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Marvel Team-Up feat. Spider-Man and Iron Fist (31), March 1975; 212290 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Marvel Team-Up feat. Spider-Man and Iron Fist (63), November 1977; 212291 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Marvel Two-in-One Presents The Thing and Iron Fist (25), March 1977; 212292 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Subseries D: Master of Kung Fu, 212174
    - Master of Kung Fu (90-93), July- October 1980; 212299 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Master of Kung Fu (94-96), November 1980- January 1981; 212300 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Master of Kung Fu (97-101), 1981; 212301 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Subseries E: Nick Fury Agent of S.H.E.I.L.D., 212175
    - Strange Tales- Nick Fury Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D. (145), June 1966; 212302 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Nick Fury Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D. and Doctor Strange (160- 163), September- December 1967; 212303 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Nick Fury Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D. and Doctor Strange (164-167), January- April 1968; 212304 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Subseries F: Shogun Warriors, 212178
    - Shogun Warriors (1-6), February- July 1979; 212305 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Shogun Warriors (8-10), September- November 1979; 212306 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Shogun Warriors (12, 14, 16-18, 20), January- September 1980; 212307 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Subseries G: The Tomb of Dracula, 212309
    - The Tomb of Dracula (21, 37-39), June 1974- December 1975; 212319 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - The Tomb of Dracula (20, 40-42), May 1974- March 1976; 212320 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Subseries H: Mantis, 212308
    - Giant- Size Avengers (3,4), February- June 1975; 212317 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - The Avengers (114, 123, 124, 138, 131-133), August 1973- March 1975; 212318 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Subseries I: Spiderman, 212179
    - Spiderman and the Black Widow, May 1977; 212311 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Marvel Team-Up feat. Spider-Man and the Daughters of the Dragon (64), December 1977; 212312 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Marvel Team-Up feat. Spider-Man and Moon Dragon (44), April 1976; 212313 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Marvel Team-Up feat. Spiderman and Sons of the Tiger (40), December 1975; 212314 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Marvel Team-Up starring Spider-Man and the X-Men (1), 1976; 212315 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Subseries J: World's Finest, 212310
    - World's Finest (222,232), 1974-1975; 212316 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - World's Finest (234), December 1975; 212321 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Subseries K: Various Comics, 212180
    - Dragon Lord (5), March 1980; 212323 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - The Eternals (11), May 1977; 212324 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - The Hands of Shang-Chi Master of Kung Fu (43), August 1976; 212325 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - The Invaders (26,38,41), March- September 1979; 212326 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - It! The Living Colossus (23,24), April- June 1974; 212327 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Luke Cage, Power Man (1), 1976; 212328 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Marvel Triple Action (12), August 1973; 212329 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Power Man (49), February 1978; 212330 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Sgt. Fury and His Howling Commandos, October 1971; 212331 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Uncanny Tales from the Grave, June 1975; 212332 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Series III: DC Asian (By Character), 212181
  - Subseries A: Chop Chop, 212182
    - Modern Comics (79,89,94), November 1948- February 1950; 212497 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Blackhawk (82, 107, 233, 236, 239), November 1954- March 1968; 212498 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Blackhawk (241, 244, 245), July 1968- April 1976; 212499 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Blackhawk (246- 250), June 1976- February 1982; 212500 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Blackhawk (251, 252, 264), October 1982- November 1983); 212501 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Four Star Spectacular (Superboy) (6), January 1977; 212502 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Batman and Blackhawk (167), October 1980; 212503 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Karate Kid, 212183
    - Karate Kid (1-4), April- October 1976; 212504 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Karate Kid (5-9), December 1976- August 1977; 212505 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Karate Kid (10-15), October 1977- August 1978; 212506 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Superboy (210), August 1975; 212507 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Subseries C: Korak, Son of Tarzan, 212184
    - Korak... Son of Tarzan (55,56), 1974; 212508 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D: Kung Fu Fighter, 212185
    - Kung-Fu Fighter (1-4), May- Novemeber 1975; 212509 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Kung-Fu Fighter (5-8), January- May 1976; 212510 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Kung-Fu Fighter (9-13), June 1976- February 1977; 212511 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Kung-Fu Fighter (14-17), April- October 1977; 212512 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Batman and Kung-Fu Fighter (132), February 1977; 212513 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Series IV: DC Asian (By Comic), 212186
  - Subseries A: Batman, 212187
    - Batman (242-244), 1972; 212514 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Batman (253), Novemeber 1973; 212515 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Batman (236), May- June (1974); 212516 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Batman (237), July- August 1974; 212517 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Batman (284- 285), February- March 1977; 212518 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Batman (330, 333- 335), 1980- 1981; 212519 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Detective Comics: Batman (354), August 1966; 212520 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Detective Comics (The Batman) (439), February- March 1974; 212521 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Detective Comics (Batman) (485, 487, 500), 1979- 1981; 212522 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Detective Comics Starring Batman (547), 1985; 212523 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Detective Comics Presents Batman and Batgirl (405), Novemeber 1970; 212524 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Detective Comics: Batman and Batgirl (408), February 1971; 212525 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Detective Comics Presents: Batman and Batgirl (411), May 1971; 212526 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Batman with Robin (232, 235, 240), 1971-1972; 212527 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Detective Comics Presents: Batman and Robin (399), May 1970; 212528 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Batman and the Spectre (75), January 1967; 212529 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Batman and the Spectre (180), November 1981; 212530 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Batman and the New Wonder Woman (87), January 1970; 212531 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Batman and the Demon (187), October 1977; 212532 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Batman Family (9), February 1977; 212533 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - The Untold Legend of the Bat Man (2), August 1980; 212534 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Batman and the Outsiders (1), 1984; 212535 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Batman and the Outsiders (11,18), 1984- 1985; 212536 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Subseries B: GI Combat, 212188
    - G.I. Combat (22,118), September 1980, July 1966; 212537 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - G.I. Combat (174,177,186), January 1976; 212538 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - G.I. Combat (223, 239), March 1982; 212539 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Subseries C. Iron Man, 212189
    - The Invincible Iron Man (4), 1977; 212540 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - The Invinsible Iron Man (30, 39-40, 47, 53), October 1970- December 1972; 212541 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Iron Man (72), January 1975; 212542 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Iron Man (73-76), March- July 1975; 212543 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Iron Man (77, 78, 81), August 1975- December 1975; 212544 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Iron Man (130), January 1980; 212545 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Iron Man (144), March 1981; 212546 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - The Spirit (8), 1985; 212547 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Subseries D: Jonah Hex, 212190
    - Jonah Hex (42), November 1980; 212548 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Jonah Hex (43-46), December 1980- March 1981; 212549 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Jonah Hex (47-52), April 1981- Septemeber 1981; 212550 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Jonah Hex (60-63), May 1981- August 1982; 212551 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Subseries E: Justice League of America, 212191
    - Justice League of America (57), November 1967; 213798 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Justice League of America (75, 82, 86), November 1969- December 1970; 213799 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Subseries F: Shadow, 212192
    - The Shadow (1-3), October 1973- March 1974; 213800 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Shadow (4-7), April 1974- March 1975; 213801 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Shadow (8-12), April- September 1975; 213802 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Subseries G: Shazam!, 212193
    - Shazam! (12), May- June 1974; 213803 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - With One Magic Word: Shazam! (14), September- October 1974; 213804 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Shazam! (20), October 1975; 213805 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Shazam! (25), October 1976; 213806 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Subseries H: Star Fire, 212194
    - Starfire (1-5), September 1976- May 1977; 213807 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Starfire (6-8), July 1976- May 1977; 213808 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Subseries I: Unexpected, 212195
    - Unexpected (138), August 1972; 213809 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Unexpected (216), November 1981; 213810 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Subseries J: Weird War Tales, 212196
    - Weird War Tales (34, 43, 59, 75), 1975- 1979; 213811 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Weird War Tales (93, 96, 100), November 1980- June 1981; 213812 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Subseries K: Wonder Woman, 212197
    - Wonder Woman (158- 166), 1956- 1966; 213813 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Wonder Woman (178, 180-183), 1968-1969; 213814 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Wonder Woman (184, 186-189), 1969-1970; 213815 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Wonder Woman (196- 200), 1971-1972; 213816 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Wonder Woman (201-203), 1972; 213817 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Wonder Woman (214, 221, 237, 238, 241), 1974- 1978; 213818 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Wonder Woman (268, 283, 284, 285), June 1980- November 1981; 213819 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Subseries L: Various Characters and Comics, 212198
    - Action Comics (363), May 1968; 213820 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Adventure Comics (Aquaman) (476), October 1980; 213821 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Air War Stories (Kamikaze!) (6), February 1966; 213822 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - All- Star Squadron (42), February 1984; 213823 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Anthro (6), July- August 1969; 213824 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Arak: Son of Thunder (48), September 1985; 213825 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Arion, Lord of Atlantis (1,20), 1984- 1985; 213826 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Blitzkrieg (2), March- April 1976; 213827 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Captain Marvel (14), 1942; 213828 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - The Creeper (4), December 1968; 213829 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Doorway to Nightmare (4), August 1978; 213830 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - The Flash (180, 181), 1968; 213831 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Ghosts (35), 1975; 213832 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Infinity Inc. (17), August 1985; 213833 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - The Mighty Isis (1-4), November 1976- May 1977; 213834 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - The Joker (1,3), Undated; 213835 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Kung- Fu Fighter (12), November 1976; 213836 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Legion of Superheroes (13), August 1985; 213837 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - The Losers (154, 170), 1976- 1976; 213838 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Metal Men (20, 27), 1966-1967; 213839 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Phantom Stranger (1,20,31,39), 1969-1975; 213840 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Rag Man (2,3), 1976- 1977; 213841 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Secrets of Haunted House (32), January 1981; 213842 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Secret Six (4), October- November 1968; 213843 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Our Army at War feat. SGT. Rock (257), June 1973; 213844 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Sherlock Holmes (1), October 1975; 213845 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Star Trek (20), 1985; 213846 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Strange Adventures (215, 216), December 1968- February 1969; 213847 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Strange Sports (2,6), 1973- 1974; 213848 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Superboy and the Legion of Superheroes (238), January 1978; 213849 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Supergirl (7) (Adventure Comics no. 418), 1972- 1973; 213850 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Superman (153), May 1962; 213851 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Superman's Pal Jimmy Olsen (157, 159, 163), March 1973- March 1974; 213852 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Sword of Sorcery (1-5), March- December 1973; 213853 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Vigilante (19,23), 1985; 213854 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Tarzan Presents Edgar Rise Burroughs Weird Worlds (6), August 1973; 213855 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Weird Worlds Presents Iron Wolf (8-20), November 1973- November 1974; 213856 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Wings Comics (26), 1942; 213857 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Series V: Deadly Hands of Kung Fu, 167441
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu: Special Album Edition (1), 1974; 213858 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu (1,2), April 1974- June 1974; 213859 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu (3-5), August 1974- October 1974; 213860 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu (6-10), November 1974- March 1975; 213861 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu (11-14), April- July 1975; 213862 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu (15), Summer 1975; 213863 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu (16-19), September 1975- December 1975; 213864 (Box 5, Folder 7)